（古市）＜皆さん　お元気ですか？
古市です。→
How are you doing, everyone? Furuichi here.
今日は街に繰り出し　素敵な
ひと時を過ごしています。→
Today I have come to the city and
am spending a lovely time here.
いつもの　おっさんは
どうしたかって？→
"Where's the big guy that's
always around?" you ask?
フッ。どっかの
バカじゃあるまいし→
I'm nobody's fool!
そう何度も同じ間違いは
繰り返しませんよ。今頃…→
That's right! I won't make
the same mistake again.
Right about now...
買い物の荷物持ちを
しているはずです＞
...he should carrying all the shopping!
（古市）
＜さあ　今日こそはシティボーイ
古市貴之の素敵な…＞
Now, it's time for city-boy
Furuichi Takayuki's wonderful...
（アランドロン）マハッ！
（古市）えっ！？
（グラスが割れる音）
古市殿。このベッドなのですが
いかがですか？
Furuichi-dono... What do
you think of this bed?
（古市）はっ！？
いえね…今　我々が２人で
使っているベッドが手狭だと→
You see, I mentioned that the bed we use at
the moment is a tad narrow to your mother,
お母様に言ったら　買ってあげるとおっしやって下さって。
and she went and bought this for us!
（女子大生）２人で…わおっ
！
The two of them? Wow...
（女子大生）
今どきの子は違うわね～。
Kids these days sure have different tastes!
（女子大生たち）ウフフッ…。
さ！ためしに
寝てみましょう…古市殿？
Now, let us try sleeping together on it!
Furuichi-dono!
うわぁあああ～～！！
I've Quit Being the BoB Brawler!
（東条）…んだ　これ。
What the hell?
（不良一同）部下にして下さい！
Please, make us your underlings!
（東条）あん？
（不良）一年の男鹿って奴が
最近　調子に乗ってんすよ！
This first-year, Oga, has
been on a tear lately!
（不良）
この前も男鹿がマカオの力を使って
暴れまわって…やべ～よ。→
The other day he used Macao
power to go on a rampage!
It was horrible, man! The combination of
Macao and morning-glorys was... horrible!
朝顔とマカオのコンボ
やべ～よ～！
へえ～…。じゃあ　こいつは
男鹿がやったってのか。
So it was Oga that did this?
（不良）ここは　手ぇ組んで男鹿を
やってやりましょうよ！
Let's join together and take down Oga!
わりぃが　部下とか
そ～いうのに興味はねぇな。→
Sorry, but I'm not interested
in having underlings and stuff.
他　当たりな。
（不良一同）お願いします！
Try someone else.
Please!
（不良）もう　東条さんしか
いねぇんすよ！
You're the only one left, Tojo-san!
チッ！わ～ったよ。
頑張ったらな。
Fine, I get it. Do your best.
≪えっ！≫
えっ…頑張ったらって　何を？
Do our best? At what...?
（東条）い～から　適当に頑張れよ。
おら　散れ散れ。
Whatever, just... Try hard at stuff.
Now scram.
（不良一同）う…うっす！
Right!
フフッ…。
（蝉の鳴き声）
Hot...
（男鹿）あちい…
あちい　あちい　あちい…。
Hot, hot, hot...
何なんだ　この異常な暑さは…。
What the hell is with this freaky heat?
（ベル坊）ダブ…。
エアコンも効きやしねぇ。
The air conditioner isn't doing a damn thing.
…って３８度！？マジで！？
38 degrees?! Seriously?
これ　あれか。
地球温暖化ってやつか…→
Is this that global warming thing?
こりゃあ　魔王が何かしなくても
地球滅びるな。
At this rate the world'll be destroyed
whether or not I deal with this Demon Lord thing.
（美咲）おはよ～　ああ～
…って　暑！何　この部屋！
Good morning.
It's hot! What the hell's with this room?
あん？
（ヒルダ）ふぁ…。
Good morning.
おはようございます…って　暑！
Whoa, it's hot!
ああ？
ううっ…ううっ…。
A summer cold?
夏風邪？
…のようなものですね。
That is how it seems.
こいつのせいかよ。
ふ～ん。
It's his fault?
Hey, Baby Beel... You hot?
Have an ice cream pop...
ほ～ら　ベル坊　暑いか？
アイスだぞ～。
（アイスの溶ける音）
（美咲）あっ…。
あれま…最近の子は
気合い入ってるわね～。
Well, damn.
Kids these days sure get all fired up.
氷枕あったっけな～。
Did we have an ice pack somewhere?
う～っ…。
おい　大丈夫なのかよ　これ。→
Hey, is this gonna be okay?
このまま　街を灼熱に
変えるとかじゃね～だろうな。
The city isn't gonna end up flame
broiled at this rate, right?
心配いらん。
恐らく一過性のものだろう。
No need to worry. It is
likely only temporary.
冷やせば　おさまる。
ただ　時期が少し気になるが…。
It will pass if we cool him.
However, the season is somewhat curious...
時期？
Season?
（古市）ああ～…。
古市！いいとこに来た！→
Furuichi!
You came just at the right time!
ちょうど　お前を呼び出そうと
思ってたとこだ。→
I was just going to call you over.
見ろ　ベル坊が夏風邪でよ。
Look, Baby Beel's got a summer fever.
東条　探すぞ。
んっ…あん？東条？
Go find Tojo!
Tojo?
もうなあ…
ギリギリなんだよ…色々と→
I'm about to go over the edge!
Like, in all kinds of ways!
俺は　俺の青春は…つか
俺のキャラクターがなぁ～！
My... My youth!
My very character!
（美咲）おっ　たかちんじゃん！久しぶり！
Oh, if it isn't Takachin! Long time!
氷枕なかったんだけどさ～
こんなもん見つけちゃった。→
Didn't have an ice pack, but I did find this.
ビニールプール　こいつに
氷浮かべて冷やすべ。
An inflatable pool.
We can cool him down by giving
him an ice bath in this!
いやいや　おかしいだろ　アネキ…。冷やせば何でもいいってわけじゃ。
Wait, that's just weird, Sis.
I mean, it's not like we can use
just anything to cool him down...
（美咲）暑いから　ついでに
あたしも入っかなぁ～。→
It's hot out, so maybe I'll get in myself.
ヒルダちゃん
水着　持ってたっけ？
Hilda-chan, did you have a swimsuit?
（古市）うっ。ああ　いえ。持ってませんが…。
No, I do not.
（美咲）ああ。じゃあ　適当に貸すよ。いやだからな～。
Oh, then I'll lend you one of mine.
But look, wait...
俺　膨らましますよ。
おい　古市！
I'll blow it up!
Hey, Furuichi...
Shut up!
うるせ～！お前に
俺の苦しみがわかるか！？
How could you understand my suffering?
海もダメ　高原もダメ
街もダメ…これ以上→
The beach is out, the highlands
are out, the city is out...
If you destroy my reputation any more,
俺の尊厳を傷つけると　何するか
わかんねぇ～ぞ　こらぁ！
I can't be held responsible for my actions!
…ったく。東条の話は　どうした？
（古市）おら　何やってんだ　男鹿！手伝え～！
Sheesh...
What happened to the Tojo thing?
What are you doing, Oga? Help me!
（不良）それ…フッ！…うっ！
（殴る音）
（不良）ひっ～…うっ。
（東条）フフッ…。
（不良）うっ。
（殴る音）
（不良）あっ…ああ…。
（相沢）
相変わらず　一方的っすね。→
Just as one-sided as ever...
まっ　東条さん相手に
この程度の人数じゃあな…。
Well, these few aren't going to
be a match for you, Tojo-san.
（陣野）バイトは　どうした？
What about the part-time job?
いや　そのバイトで　こいつらを
十人抜きしたら　絡んできてよ。
Well, after pinning 10 guys' arms
down, they all came after me.
Arm Wrestling
1 100 Yen/Try
（相沢）
んっ？嬉しそうっすね。
手応えのある連中だったんすか？
You seem happy.
Were they actually decently tough?
いや　そうじゃね～よ。
なあ　庄次。→
No, that's not it.
It seems like Oga was making
trouble again, Shoji.
この前　男鹿が派手に
暴れたらしいぞ。
（相沢）えっ？
Just like the rumors say, he's tough.
（東条）噂通り　骨のある奴
みて～だ。
んん…。
楽しみでよ～。
I can't wait!
そろそろ　いいわよ。辰巳。
It's almost ready, Tatsumi!
Sure.
おう！…熱っ！
うう～…。
（お湯の沸く音）
ええっ！？
（古市）一瞬で熱湯に…。
Boiling it instantly?
ええ～っ！？…ったく　どんだけ
気合い入ってんのよ。この子…→
Sure there's fired up,
but this is ridiculous!
He's not going to cool off like this...
これじゃあ　涼めないじゃん！
いや　いや　いや…。
No, no, no...
（古市）ない　ない　ない。
Not going to happen!
（古市）ま…待って下さい！
涼めなくとも→
Please, wait!
Even if we can't cool him down, we
could at least use it as a hot tub!
せめて　風呂替わりに入るとか…。
You wish for a hot bath, do you?
（アランドロン）
お風呂をご所望ですかな？えっ！？
はい　来た～！
He's here!
Then why don't we go to our house's bath?
（アランドロン）では　我が家のお風呂場に参りましょう。→
お背中を　お流ししますぞ～。
い…いや。
I'll scrub your back for you!
（古市）違う　違う～！
（アランドロン）はっはっはっ…違うの？
はっ　はははっ…。
何なんだ…つ～か。
What was that about?
Anyway...
ふう…。
本当に大丈夫なんだろうな。うん…。
Is this really gonna be okay?
うっ　うっ…。
（哺乳瓶が割れる音）
あっ！
おい　何やってんだ。
床が　びしょ濡れじゃね～か。
Hey, what are you doing?
The floor's sopping wet...
うむ…。ミルクが一瞬にして
沸騰してしまった。あん？
The milk boiled instantly...
もう　部屋が熱くないだろう。
どうやら→
The room isn't hot anymore, yes?
It seems like the heat is
no longer escaping his body.
体の外に
熱を放出しなくなった分→
体内では信じられんほどの
高熱になっているようだ。
It has heated the inside of his
body to incredible temperatures...
ううっ…。
まずいのか？
わからん。こんな事は初めてだ…。
Is that a bad thing?
I don't know.
This has never happened before.
おっ！
おおっ。
ダッ！
おおっ！まだまだ
いけるアピールしてんぞ！
He's telling us that he's still
got another round in him!
さすがです　坊っちゃま。
それでこそ魔王！
Master, I knew you had it in you!
You do the name of Demon Lord proud!
ダッ！
飛んだっ！
He jumped!
アイッ　アイ～！
流れるようなフットワーク！
アイ～！
What flowing footwork!
ダ～ッ…アイ～！
おい…大丈夫か　これ。
明らかに　おかしいぞ。
う…うむ。
Hey, is he really okay?
Something is obviously wrong.
んっ…あっ！
んっ！？
これは…ゼブルスペルが…。
This is... The Zebel Spell is...
ハァ…ハァ～…アイ～ッ！
ハッ！
坊っちゃま！
Master!
どうやら　事態は思ったより
深刻なようだな。
His condition is far more
serious than I thought.
深刻？
右手を見てみろ。
Serious?
Look at your right hand.
あん？
おおっ！
ゼブルスペルが消えている。
The Zebel Spell has disappeared.
それは貴様と坊っちゃまの
リンクが切れている証拠。→
That proves that the link between
you and the master has disappeared.
つまり…坊っちゃまは今　魔力を
出したくても出せない状態なのだ。
In other words, even if he wanted to let out
magic power, it has no where to go at the moment.
アウ～　アウ～…。
《おいおい　マジか？》
Wait, seriously?
恐らく　この高熱も
そのせいなのだろうが…。
Perhaps this high fever is because of that.
《…ってことは
あのクソいまいましい→
That means no more god damn
annoying shock sessions!
ビリビリも
ないってことだよな？》
で…治るのか？
So, can we cure him?
わからん…。
そもそも原因からして…。
I don't know. Without understanding
the reason for it...
あん？夏風邪じゃね～のか？
…と思っておったのだが。
Huh? It's not a summer cold?
That's what I had thought, however...
放っといたら　ヤバイのか？
わからん…。
Will it get worse if we don't do anything?
I don't know!
まっ　でも　どうせ死ぬわけじゃ
ねぇんだろ…魔王なんだし。
Well, it's not like he's
gonna die. He's a Demon Lord!
わからんと言っておろ～が！
I told you, I don't know, damn it!
なっ！
なんだよ。
急に大声　出しやがって…。
Why're you yelling all of a sudden?
んっ？…でも待てよ？
っていうことは　あれか？→
But, wait...
Doesn't this mean...?
もしかして　今なら１５ｍ以上
離れても大丈夫なんじゃね？
Does this mean I'll be okay farther
than 15 meters from him now?
どこへなりと
消え失せるがいいっ！
Go off somewhere and vanish from this world!
うわ～～！！
て…てめえ！
いきなり　なんてこと…。
What the hell was that for?
出てゆけ。
Get out.
えっ！
You disappoint me.
貴様には失望した…
二度と帰ってくるな。
Never come back here again!
…のやろう。何が出てゆけだ→
That bitch, what the hell is
she telling me to leave for?
てめ～の家じゃね～っつ～の。
バカ女。
That ain't your house, you idiot!
((ヒィ～…))
大体　魔王が死のうが
どうしよ～が→
I mean, what's it to me if a
Demon Lord or two kicks it?
俺の知ったこっちゃね～しな
つ～か…むしろ　いい事じゃん。
And wait, isn't this is a good thing?
あ～　せいせいしたぜ。
I feel so refreshed!
ヒェ～ヒェ～…。
坊っちゃま。
Master...
このヒルダ…命にかえても。
Even if it costs me my
life, I, Hilda, will...
ちっ…ああ～クソ！
Damn it!
あん？
よお！
Yo.
うっ！
何だあ？
この程度かよ。男鹿辰巳。
What? Is that all you got, Oga Tatasumi?
（相沢）これじゃあ　東条さんと
やるには足りねぇな～。
That's not going to satisfy Tojo-san...
うっ…。
なんだ　てめえは…。
Who the hell are you?
フッ…。
ペッ！東条っつったか　今？
Did you just say Tojo?
Oh, you can stand? That's good, good...
お～　立っちゃうの？いいねいいね
そうこなくちゃ→
It wouldn't be any fun otherwise, Oga-kun.
つまんねえよな　男鹿くん。
ウッ！
ハハ…危ね。
That was close.
ウッ！
悪くないが　まだまだ…。
Not bad, but you got a long way to go.
ウッ！
終わりか？
That's it?
He's strong!
≪こいつ　強ええ…≫
ウッ！
（携帯の着信音）
Yes, this is Aizawa. How do you do?
はいよ　相沢。毎度　はい…。→
Yes. Yes...
はい…どええっ！マジですか！？
了解　すぐ行きます。
Seriously?!
Roger that. I'll be right there.
悪いな。急用が入っちまった。
Sorry, I've got an emergency here...
Let's play again sometime.
また今度　遊ぼうぜ。
待てよ！
Wait!
てめえ　東条の何なんだ？
What's your relationship to Tojo?
（相沢）手下その１ってとこかな。
じゃ　またね！
His number one man, I suppose.
See you later then.
ただいま～っと！
I'm home...
アー…。
That stupid woman...
あのバカ女。ベル坊ほったらかしに
して　どこ行きやがった！？
Where the hell did she go,
leaving Baby Beel here?
イー…。
う～…。ったく　あんなに
大騒ぎしてたくせによ。
Man... And after she made such a fuss.
（いびき）
イー…。
ダー…。
ん？ベル坊…。
Baby Beel?
いなくなった？
ベル坊とヒルダさんが？
Baby Beel and Hilda-san are gone?
Yup. When I woke up this
morning, not a sign of them.
ああ！朝起きたら
きれいさっぱりと。
Not a sign? What are you going to do?
「さっぱり」って
お前　どうすんだよ？
Huh? Nothing in particular.
あん？別に　どうもしねえよ。
むしろ　いねえ方が…。
I mean, I'm better off without...
辰巳～！！あんた
何やってんのよ！？
Tatsumi!
What the hell did you do?
Hilda-san and Baby Beel are gone, you say?
ヒルダちゃんとベル坊
いなくなったって～！？
You'll never find a wife as
good as her anywhere else!
あんな出来た嫁さん
どこ探したって　いないわよ！
Sis...
ちょ…姉貴！
（美咲）わかってんの！？
You understand?
I'm telling you...
だから…。
（美咲）どうせ　つまんないことして
愛想つかされたんでしょ！
You obviously did something stupid,
and she got fed up with you!
That's not it!
ちが…。
（美咲）謝ってきなさい！
Hurry up and apologize!
Why me too?
（古市）何でオレまで！？
Listen up! Until you bring them back,
I'm not letting you into the house!
いい！？ちゃんと探して
連れてくるまで→
家には　入れないからね！
She's as tough as ever...
（古市）相変わらず　おっかねえな。
Damn it... I'm finally free, and...
ったく　せっかく
手に入れた自由だぞ。
Who the hell would go searching for them?
誰が　わざわざ探すかっての。
あ～　あっちいな。
川原にでも行くか。
川原？
It's hot! Let's go to the river or something.
The river?
So he is searching for them...
≪結局　探すんじゃん≫
おっ　東条さん
噂をすればっすよ。
Tojo-san, speak of the devil.
あん？
ほ～　お前が男鹿か。→
Oh, so you're Oga.
思ったより細えな。
You're thinner than I thought.
It's finally time! Let's fight.
ようやくだ。ケンカしよ～ぜ。
（古市）≪あれが東条…って
あれ　ベル坊だよな？→
That's Tojo...
And wait, isn't that Baby Beel?
何で　東条の背中に？≫
Why is he on Tojo's back?
Oga's... getting pissed?
≪男鹿　ムカついてる？
いや　わかんね～な。→
No, I can't tell...
This is basically like our wish come true...
状況的には　願ったり
かなったりなわけだし→
He'll probably say something like "Lucky!"
こいつなら「ラッキー！」
くらい言いそうだ≫
ラ…ラッキー。
あ？
Lucky!
見たまえ古市君
何か知らんが　あのガキ→
Check it out, Furuichi-kun!
I don't know exactly why, but that
brat is latched onto Tojo, my lad!
東条に　ひっついて
いるのですぞ！
ですぞ？
My lad?
押し付ける手間が
省けたってもんだ。帰るぞ！
Now we're saved the trouble of
pushing him off onto someone.
We're going back!
Go back where?
おい　どこ帰るつもりだよ？
あ？帰るっつったら
家に決まってんだろ！
I mean I'm going home, of course!
That's the river!
そっちは川だ。
バカ野郎！川だって家だ！
Idiot! The river is home!
な　何言ってんの？
What the hell are you...?
ハハハ！おもしれえ野郎だな。
You're one funny bastard.
This guy's a real piece of work, Shoji.
なあ庄次　あれは大物だぜ。
I wonder...
ど～っすかね　別に
止めやしませんけど。→
I'm not going to stop you,
but I don't think he's really a person
that'll be a good match for you, Tojo-san.
俺には　東条さんが相手するほどの
ヤツには　見えませんでしたがね。
フ…そいつは
やってみてのお楽しみだ。
Well, I look forward to finding out.
いいから落ち着けって！
ん？
Just calm down, okay?
You have to make sure first!
とにかく　まずは確認が先だ！
ベル坊は　本当に→
Is Baby Beel really with Tojo now?
東条のもとに行ったのか。
If you wanna freak out, do
it after you've made sure!
あせんのは　それを確かめて
からでも　遅くねえだろ！
I'm not freaking out, okay?
だから　別にあせってねえよ！
Tojo-san, can we ask you something?
東条さん
ひとつ聞いていいっすか？
（東条）あん？
Sure.
背中の子って　東条さんの子っすか？
最近拾ったとか　くっついて→
Is that baby on your back yours, Tojo-san?
Or did you just pick him up somewhere,
and he's stuck to your back?
離れないとか　そういう
わけじゃ　ないですか？
ああ…こいつか？
Oh, this guy?
Yeah...
そうだな　俺に勝ったら
教えてやるよ。
I'll tell you if you beat me.
クッ。
フン！いいね　目でわかるぜ。
Good. I can see it in your eyes.
お前もオレと同じ
ただのケンカ好きだ。
You're like me. You just like to fight.
あ？
（東条）自分の本気を試したくて
ウズウズしてんだろ？
You're itching to fight with
your full strength, yeah?
だが周りにゃ
弱えヤツばかりだ。
But you're surrounded only by weaklings.
全力を受け止めてくれる
ヤツなんて　そうはいねえ。
There ain't anyone who could
take you on at full power.
That's how it is for me.
オレがそうだ。
どっからでも　かかってこい。
Come at me however you want.
ふざけたヤローだ。
You're a crazy bastard...
（東条）いくぜ！
Here I come!
おいおい　ど～した？
これで終わりじゃねえだろうな。
Hey, what's wrong?
Don't tell me it's over already...
Oga got beat?
（古市）≪男鹿が押し負けた！？≫
It's over.
（相沢）≪終わりっすよ。あんたの
一撃を　まともにくらって→
No one could stand after taking
a full-on hit from you.
立ったヤツなんて…≫
うおっ！
Good. Wanna do it again?
いいね。もう一度やろうってか？
うう…らぁっっ！！
Tojo-san!
東条さん！！
Don't get excited.
騒ぐな！あ～…
面白くなってきやがった。
This has gotten interesting.
≪マジかよ！？東条さんが
ふっ飛ぶとこなんて→
Seriously? Tojo-san was knocked down?
初めて見たぞ≫
I've never seen that happen before.
よお。おめえも　そうなんだろ？
Hey. You're the same, right?
っと！
ウッ！
あ…。
You're pissin' me off...
ムカつく野郎だ！
マネすんじゃねえよ！
Stop copying me!
フン！男鹿っつったか。
下の名前は？
Oga, right? What's your first name?
あ？辰巳だ　ボケ。
Tatsumi! What's it to you?
そうか　男鹿辰巳か…。
I see... Oga Tatasumi, is it?
あぁ？
あのガキな　オレんじゃねえぜ。
ああ？
The kid ain't mine.
（東条）昨日拾っただけだ。何でか
知らねえけど迷子でな。→
I picked him up yesterday. Dunno
what happened, but he seemed lost.
I figured I'd to look after
'im till I find his parents.
仕方ねえから親が見つかるまで
面倒みようってわけだ。
聞いてねえよ。
なに勝手に答えてんだ？
I didn't ask you. Why are you answering?
まさか　お前が
親ってわけじゃねえだろうな？
Don't tell me that you're his father?
だから聞いてねえって
言ってんだろ！！
I told you... I didn't ask!
らぁぁぁっ！！
ウッ…。
あ　あれは！
That's...
≪ゼブルスペル！？≫
Zebel Spell!
礼を言うぜ　男鹿辰巳。お前の
おかげで　少し本気を出せそうだ！
I've gotta thank you, Oga Tatsumi.
Thanks to you, I think I can
actually go all out a little bit!
あ！
Here I come!
いくぞ！
あ！
おっ！？
ああ…。
ふむ…こんなもんか！
That's all he's got?
No-no-no... That was amazing, Tojo-san!
いやいやいや…
ありえないっすよ　東条さん。
ギャグマンガでしか見ないような
ふっ飛び方しましたよ！
You punched him into the
air like in some gag manga!
フン！心配すんな
川に落ちただけだ。
Don't worry, he just fell in the river.
Now, you there... Tell
him this: "It was fun."
（東条）なあ　お前
あいつに伝えときな→
「楽しかったぜ」ってな。
プハッ！
クソー！！
Shit!
Your pits sweat like I've never seen...
すげえな　お前の脇汗。
ダー…。
And there you have it! Baby Beel's
new dad is Tojo from the TKKH!
Isn't that nice, Oga?
No, it's not! I'm not
going to let it end here!
I'm gonna beat the crap outta this Tojo guy!
There is only one way to save the master!
But it is a way so dangerous, it
risks your very life, Oga-dono!
Fine by me!
On the next Beelzebub:
The Doctor Has Arrived.
Wait a sec... If a doctor is here,
did he bring a pretty nurse?